Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun!
Friendship, love, courage,
and a little bit of fun!
These are the things!
That even as the years go by!
Will not ever vanish from our minds!
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth!
Little by little we can
find each other's worth!
And as we see!
What sort of form we're meant to take!
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind to dry!
All the tears as you're breathing!
The things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger!
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember!
Everything, everything, everything!
Now and forever!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind
to dry all the tears!
As you're blaving the
things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
All units, load up, move out!
Use your prison bullets!
Prepare to deal with Devil Fruit powers!
We've reached level 6, sir!
Move in!
What the heck is that?
The ceiling?
Worry about that later!
Spread out and search the floor!
Do you really think they stuck around
here after making that gigantic hole?
You morons!
Shiryu, the jail manager!
Pathetic!
It's as plain as day!
You can't do anything right without me!
What a bunch of sorry excuses for jailers!
Let me give you a hint!
So maybe you can clean up this disgrace!
While you were picking your noses!
The three prisoners you're looking for!
Release Crocodile and Jinbei!
and then climbed up through
that hole to level five.
I want you to pass along a message for me.
Tell Magellan I'll help him if he wants.
No, that's, uh...
What?
What did you say?
They've escaped with Jinbei and Crocodile?
Yes, sir.
They're not in their cells.
No!
Are you saying that even
after my brilliant plan,
they somehow learned their
way out of level six?
And now they're a group
of five roaming wild
and not sleeping like
they're supposed to be?
Yes, sir, that's correct.
Do you think I might be held
responsible for any of this nonsense?
Warden Magellan is currently
transporting Portgas D .A .s to the Navy,
so I'm afraid you'd be
responsible for all of it.
I knew you were gonna say that!
All right, I'm gonna get
out there and fight, too.
All jailers report to Level 4 immediately.
Mr.
Sadie, Saldeff.
Gather your forces and head
to Level 4 this instant.
I'll be warden even if
I have to risk my life.
Wait, what am I saying?
Stop those criminals even if
you have to risk your lives!
Is everybody ready?
Just so you know, even if we do
make it to the top of the prison,
we'll still be in for one hell of a fight.
We're completely surrounded
by the Calm Belt,
which is impassable in any normal ship.
We'll have to steal a Navy vessel if we
want to go anywhere near their headquarters.
That means we need more
people to join our team.
I know what you're thinking,
we have lots already.
But to be honest, some of
you won't make it out alive.
By the time we reach the top floor,
many of you won't be there to see it.
If you're captured, you'll
be tortured to death.
There will be no mercy.
So if we want to survive,
we need to set free as
many prisoners as possible
while we make our way
from here to level one.
Whether we like them or
not, we'll need their help.
If we can cause enough
chaos to start a riot,
it'll help keep those jailers occupied.
That means our first step
on each floor is to open
the cells and let our new
friends clear the way for us.
So let's give these boys hell!
Newcomer Land is going
to rattle this big cage
the likes of which
they've never seen before!
Hee-haw!
Are you ready to rock this Straw Hat, boy?
He went on ahead of us.
A free spirit. Hee-haw!
Let's catch up to him, candies!
Please, somebody please stop me!
I'm going too fast!
It's never been this past before!
Mom, the hormone seems to
be working a bit over time.
Indeed, but check out those amazing moves.
Very nice.
It's not nice!
I'm getting sick!
It's just before 10 in the morning.
The execution is at 3 in the afternoon.
We can be certain that they'll do
everything in their power to stay on time.
So if Whitebeard is
going to make an attack,
it's most likely that he'll
do it as soon as possible.
Ace should already be on
the ship and en route.
The war could break out at any second.
But they won't kill him
until three o 'clock, right?
That means we still have a
chance to get there and save him!
Yes.
Is this supposed to slow me down?
I'll use my right hand
and turn this into sand.
Let's go over how Crocodile's
Sansan devil crew power works.
He can turn into sand
as well as control it.
His right hand can suck
out any type of moisture.
People and plants will wither away, while
rocks and earth will turn into sand.
They're here!
Level 4 reporting in.
Jinbei, the warlord who escaped
from Level 6 has been sighted.
Seems we've reached the burning heat hell.
Alongside the intruder monkey, D.
Luffy.
Man, it's hot.
The former warlord
crocodile is here as well.
We're prepared to engage the enemy. Fire!
Idiots!
Use the prison bullet!
Far gone!
Fire the prison bullets!
Here we go!
Come on, please!
Fishman Karate!
Karate!
Huh?
What just happened?
Feel my arabesque brick fist!
Straw Hat 2, Warlords?
What are we supposed to do?
We don't stand a chance!
Don't give up!
We outnumber them at least!
We need to hold out until
the reinforcements arrive!
Move it!
We're in a rush.
Should be fun!
There's a lot of commotion.
They just made an announcement,
but I couldn't hear it.
Perhaps something big
is happening downstairs.
Hey, take a look, Buggy.
All the jailers in the blue
corner are making a retreat.
All prison staff, head down to level four.
Something big must be happening
on one of the other levels.
Now's our chance to make
a break for it, partner.
It's like a dream come true.
We've been through so much, haunted
by the army wolves in level five.
Between the wolves and the ground!
And the latest indignity,
pretending to be part of the
floor to escape the wild beasts.
We've been stuck in some cruel cosmic
joke as nothing but comic relief.
But we made it all the way to level two.
Just a little bit further now,
and we'll be out of this hellhole.
Well, boys, ready to break out.
Ready as ever.
My compliments to Mr.
Three on these wax keys.
Some fine craftsmanship right here.
All guards report to level four.
Get me, team, in here.
Come in, Vice Warden.
This is the monitoring room.
Please come in.
What's wrong?
This looks strange what?
No, no!
It's not as weird as it looks.
I'll explain.
You see,
I secretly ordered this
fancy headdress to more
clearly assert my authority
when I became warden.
That's all.
I'm not talking about
your weird headdress.
We've got a visual feed on someone
sneaking around on level to.
And they look like prisoners.
Holy
crap! The keys.
Now we can get out.
Thanks, buddy!
You don't know how?
Oh, it's your crocodile.
I'm thinking about freaking
out of here, but I might need a
bit of assistance.
And you, you're a man of
action, aren't you, Mr. One?
Now that you mention it,
things are a bit boring here.
I think I might take you up
on that offer, old friend.
Thanks, buddy.
Don't thank me.
Thank Captain Buggy.
Any guards left on two? Anyone?
Answer me if you're still there.
Yes, sir.
Are you doing anything
crucial at the moment?
Um, we were just heading down
to level four, as ordered.
Make a full inspection of
level two instead. This floor?
Now's our chance, partner.
You ready?
Once the guards are
distracted by the riot,
we'll sneak out of here and
stow away on a navy ship.
We're so close,
and we'll go down in history for
breaking out of this nightmare prison.
I'd wait just Straw Hat and Mr.
Two are already dead by now.
Either that, or they'll spend the rest
of their miserable lives in this hell.
Well, that sure is a sad thought right
there, but at least we saved our own asses.
Oh, I've got eyes on Buggy the Clown.
Level two, look up! Look up?
All right you guys if you want your
freedom back this is your chance.
Now let's tear this place apart fight
like you got nothing left to lose.
Let's kick it off give it up for
our savior yeah captain buggy.
Come in level two here i don't know how but
the prisoners are out of their cells and
They're out of control!
We need the Bacotti back!
Send backup!
Come in!
Level four here!
What is it now?
We found Ivankov and Inazuma!
Not only that, but they've got
the guy who tricked you with them!
Mr. Two!
Hee-haw!
Can't break me!
I can't break it out!
They're storming level
four with an entire mob!
What? A mob?
All staff, get down to
level four immediately!
Every available guard!
You're not gonna believe this,
but the mob they've got with them?
They're all of the missing prisoners!
The inmates who've disappeared
over the years by demoning the war!
Try checking again!
That can't be right!
I know what I'm looking at!
Yee-haw!
I finally caught up with you!
Hey, Strawboy!
Oh, Clay? Ha!
Looks like you got your
juices flowing again!
Yeah!
I'm better than ever now!
Hang on!
Why are you here, Mr. One?
You hear me?
You know that guy? Yeah! And so do you!
Your swordsman Bunny defeated
him back in Alabasta!
Oh, sorry, not ringing any bells for me.
Vice warden, we need more
backup on level four.
We also need more guys on level two.
This isn't fair.
Empire!
Face growth synthesis!
Ah!
Yee-haw!
Hurry, it's hot in here!
Hell, we!
There's too many!
We can't stop them!
They're already vicious
enough when we lock them away!
But now, they're vicious and super weird!
No time to explain,
but we can't stop them!
Let's go!
Straight to Navy Headquarters!
Yeah!
We've received word from Impel Down.
An unprecedented riot has broken
out and shut down the entire prison.
The ringleader of this revolt is
none other than Monkey D. Luffy.
Enjoy the view while you still can.
Once you've been shackled onto the
scaffold, I can promise you this.
You'll never see the sky again.
This is Onigumo.
We're now approaching.
Prepare to open the gate of Marineford.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku! How did it go?
We still haven't found him yet.
Ace's execution is five hours from now, so
we don't exactly have time in our favor.
Whitebeard could launch
an attack any moment now.
We need a warlord on our side!
We've searched the whole island!
We can't find Blackbeard.
He's gone missing.
And this could be unrelated?
But we just received word of a Navy ship!
arriving at Impel Down
without any clearance. What?
I know, sir, but what
are the chances it's him?
Please, wait a sec.
We didn't request any reinforcements.
And we're in the midst of a state of
emergency, So we can't assure your safety.
We're waiting to hear back
from headquarters at the moment
Don't go pissing your britches.
We're all on the same side.
That's not the issue
No pirate is allowed to
step foot inside the
prison even if you're on.
Don't bother holding it
back with these guys!
After all?
We're the highest ranking officials here.
Talk about a gloomy place.
Captain,
there's not a single crew member left
alive on the ship Blackbeard came in on.
They're dead?
Hey, sir!
Don't take another step!
Give an aim shot?
We have an intruder, the warlord
of the sea, Marshal D. Teach.
Hey, are you all right?
Blackbeard sucked them all
up and spit them back out.
The darkness.
Blackbeard and his crew are
breaking into the prison,
and I don't think we can stop them.
The darkness, it swallowed me up all.
His motive is unknown.
It's over.
My entire life is over.
No, I wish it was over.
This is just the beginning,
the beginning of a miserable life in
which I never get to be the warden.
I'm doomed to be the
vice warden for eternity.
Are you all right sir what the
hell's wrong with him Straw Hat
and his followers on level four
Buggy the clown leading a riot on
level two and the warlord
blackbeard busting through the main
Gates what should i do how do i
even begin to deal with this mess
This is feeling like a pretty good
time to take a snack break are you nuts
we need to save the Prison now oh
yeah that's easy enough for you to say
oh i see you want to be the vice warden
Can you hear me what warden magellan
wait where are you i'm on level two
and i've just taken care Of these
fools this floor is clear
i've
blocked
off all of the exits on level two if
the poison Hasn't stopped them yet it
will soon enough no we're completely
blocked in the doorway's clogged Of
poison what do we do captain buggy my
children you obnoxious toxic bastard
blast he'll find us If we stay here
as for blackbeard i haven't a clue
why he's attacking us but i'm already
Taking care of things it's not something
i particularly wanted to do but i
wasn't given Any other options what do
you mean it's not something you wanted
to do against better Judgment i decided
to really sheet you to deal with
them are you insane possibly but we
can't Ask navy hq for reinforcements
we're left with no choice but to deal
with this ourselves and as for You put
all of your efforts into getting level
four under control i'll be heading
down to level four Soon enough until
i get there it's your master cleaner
Ahhhh! I love you!
Order! Order!
Love the word!
Yeah, shouldn't we be going now?
Fever.
Shit, feels good to step out
of that cell, doesn't it?
Oh, yeah. It's nice.
Lesson learned, all that boredom really
makes you long for the excitement of death.
But you're not gonna use me as your pawn,
only to toss my ass back in
there once you're done with me.
Right, Magellan?
You're a condemned prisoner.
But this is your one chance,
consider it a deferred sentence.
Yeah, right.
Fine with me.
I'll make sure I'm on my best behavior.
Here's a sword. Jail manager.
As for Blackbeard, he's all yours.
Works for me.
Oh, my lovely sword.
It's been too long.
I got carried away there.
Sorry.
They broke into the jailer's
room and stole the keys!
Listen up, candy boys and candy girls!
This is a nice appetizer,
but we're going to need chaos
on every floor of this hellhole!
If you want to make it out alive,
then release every last prisoner
you can and divide the enemy forces!
If you want out now is the time this is
your best chance it's now or never guys?
Yes I'm all yours lady!
Go Blugotti!
Run wild!
Damn the Blugotti this
one's all yours guys!
nice work don't stop go and beat
that freak with a big bloated head
he's their leader hey my head is not
bloated it's face growth synthesis
All he did was wink and he
took him out in one shot!
You're kidding, I don't even get it man.
He's scary Straw Hat boy
Hurry you have to keep on running
forget about all these small fries.
We can handle them We need that
boat and we need you on it pronto.
Let's move Got it!
Thanks a lot!
It's the demon guards!
They sent three of them!
Finally, we got our backup! Mr.
Sadie is here!
This is the end of the road.
So bow down, kiss my feet,
and take your punishment.
I am admittedly better suited
to fighting underwater,
but I shall assist you as best
I can all the same, my friend.
I'm not complaining.
You seem plenty strong to me.
Go make them suffer!
Don't hold back.
Without proper eyesight, even a demon
guard is nothing more than a lumbering oaf.
Now let's get up.
How do you like the eye crusher attack?
Them all at once. Oh, oh!
Huh?
Simply pathetic.
Oh!
They're too strong! Run for it!
The candidates don't even face them!
Help!
I'm going back to my cell!
We can't win enough!
We're all gonna die!
They think they're way
stronger than the Blagoons!
Those screams!
Oh, yes!
These demon guards are
quite the formidable foe.
Third gear!
Fishman, karate!
Demon guards, fight them out!
Now come, go!
Die it!
Five thousand, quick fist!
Fables!
No! Now falter!
Raise the drawbridge.
Don't let them cross it.
Hurry up.
Stop the Blackbeard!
Fire.
He may be a warlord.
But there's no way this was sanctioned.
Blackbeard is not on our side.
He's a traitor.
Fools.
Pirates are traitors
by nature, aren't they?
Jail manager Shiryu, when
did they let you out?
Well, let's see how this goes.
Who's this putz?
Some big shit looking for trouble.
What Magellan I presume you're
Marshall D teach black beard, right?
Yep, that's me.
Who the hell are you?
This is it!
We can't fight him
without the Demon Guards!
We're screwed!
All speed ahead!
Nothing can stop us now! Crap!
It seems like their
numbers are increasing too!
Custer!
It's Team Guard ZD! Who cares?
Put you out of the way! Can it!
And that's Mistress Sadie!
Manifesto of Excitement!
Red Viper Whip!
How dare you!
Beat on my sweet little...
Minions!
Crazy lady!
Wait!
Boy, I told you to keep moving, didn't I?
Listen up, you.
You're fighting me now, naughty girl.
You know, sometimes I like a girl fight.
Stupid anarchist.
So you're a woman, like I care.
Make up your mind.
Pest.
Oh, sweetie.
Jealousy doesn't suit you.
Hurry, we're almost to the
staircase leading to level three.
I'll open the door once we're there.
Got it, let's go!
What's going on?
The door's opening by itself.
Who cares?
Good luck on our part.
Let's just get to level three.
This is the great fortress of hell.
None shall pass.
Now be gone!
Who's this, doofus?
Why'd he open the doors all the way?
That's Hannibal.
He's the vice-warden of the prison.
Fire!
Take a look!
We've got a thousand troops
armed with a thousand cage
-shot bazookas packed into
the stairway to level three.
It's the end of the line!
This is as far as you go!
In order to guarantee the safe
future of all innocent citizens,
you, Straw Hat, must be eradicated.
I hereby sentence you to
death on behalf of the Warden.
That can't be the same Vice Warden I know.
Move!
Try and make me!
He actually knows what he's doing.
And here, I thought he was
only good at complaining.
What? HENYA!
That's right, the HENYA Hustle Dance!
Infernal Hell Wheel!
Get the hell out of my way! I'll make you!
I gotta save him!
You gotta be joking!
What kind of vice-war would I be if I
stepped aside just cause an inmate asked me?
Second gear!
Now come, come!
Get off!
Get away!
We've been praying you'd arrive.
You've got to do
something, Warden Magellan.
Where are the ringleaders
behind this uprising?
They're in front of the
staircase to level three,
but that's on the opposite
side of the floor from here?
and we're going to have to
fight our way through the riot.
So far, Vice Warden
Hannibal has kept him back.
Who knows how long he can hold out?
No, Vice Warden!
Let go!
I'm not through with you yet!
You won't pass!
Follow the vice warden's lead.
Don't hold back.
You should worry about
saving your own life!
Out of my way!
Bastard.
You are not getting past me!
Shams of Jet Tail!
Don't move!
Just quit already!
Dammit!
I don't have time for this crap!
You keep saying you want to save your
brother like it's some noble quest,
but I know you're nothing but scum!
Both of you!
All the pirates and rebels here, you don't
give a damn about anyone but yourselves.
Stop by swarting you've done enough!
Don't stand up!
You're gonna get killed!
As long as scum like you are
free to terrorize the seas,
decent people can't even
sleep at night because
they're worried about
losing their loved ones.
This jail was built to protect them.
Locking up evil criminals like you is the
only way to give them some peace of mind.
This fortress is the floodgate of hell!
And I won't let the world drown in
terror by letting prisoners break free!
So like I already said, you
won't take a single step!
Bye, sport!
The only thing I want is to
save my brother, so move it!
You're too dumb to understand.
I started, help us!
Hey!
What's happening in there?
Buttercork in it already!
All this blathering about what's
right and wrong in the world.
If you'd look at the world
from outside your damn prison,
it seems not so black and white.
So cut the crap.
That guy.
I met him in Jaya!
Oh, wow! Wow!
Well, ain't this a fine
trip down memory lane!
Looks like we got you boys right
in the middle of something!
Hello, Teach.
Mind telling us what the
hell you're doing here?
Well, or do you only
answer to Blackbeard now?
Jinbei.
Hey, hey, what's with the hostility?
Why don't you loosen up those fists there?
Oh, yeah, I forgot you
and Ace are pretty tight.
But hey, there's not much point
in caring about him anymore.
Blackbeard.
I can't right now.
I'm chasing someone.
He's a pirate named Blackbeard.
The dreams of pirates will never end!
According to this,
a pirate named Blackbeard defeated Ace
and gave him up to the world government.
In return, they invited
him to be a warlord.
Blackbeard, huh?
I see...
So you're...
Blackbeard!
Huh? Oh, right.
I guess I never gave you my name, did I?
Long time no C, Straw Hat Luffy.
Hey, I know how you feel.
I was surprised myself when I heard you
were my old commander's baby brother.
What are you doing down here?
You're gonna miss the
big show don't you want
to be there for your
brother's public execution?